<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Autodidact by nature</title>
    <link>http://crisci.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Autodidact by nature</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://crisci.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Customized Widgets</title>
      <link>http://crisci.io/services/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crisci.io/services/widgets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We specialize in bespoke widgets, built to your specification.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mind behind this blog</title>
      <link>http://crisci.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crisci.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-brief-history-of-my-time-so-far&#34;&gt;A brief history of my time so far&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Laurent Crisci, autodidact by nature and always curious about the inner workings of our world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was born and mostly educated in France and having experienced the italian life for 10 years, I decided to move to England through a job opportunity since February 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been using Linux systems since 2001 as a mean to be closer to the Operating System and have a better understanding on what is really going on.
Whenever i meet something of interest, i try to understand it and can quickly end up spending a good amount of time on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it is essential to understand how things work in life as there is no magic and mostly everything has an explanation to date.
Life is a beautiful and mysterious thing that is full of surprise and continuous learning/inquiring is required to be able to discover new things which could make it better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this blog i would like to share some of my knowledge and the ongoing process that i go through to acquire new one.
I will share with you the books that i&amp;rsquo;m reading and what i thought about them, the new technologies that i have been studying and playing with and various other topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-selection-of-my-current-interests&#34;&gt;A selection of my current interests&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure As Code / Continuous Delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloud computing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Philosophy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;History&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Science&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fitness and well-being&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>